Independent Brigade is in charge of city defense.
If we want to do anti-Japanese activities in Shaanxi,
we have to deal with him.
He's a tough bone.
It's not easy to persuade him.
I'll stay and do his work alone.
Okay.
Before you can understand his mind,
I'll go around him.
I heard Chae Jin
by Chae Jin.
Is this true?
I've asked around.
It's true.
Cui Wenkui is always meticulous.
How did he offend Cai Zhen?
It is said that Chae Jin suspected that he was reduced by the Communist Party.
Cui Wenkui was annihilated by the Communist Party.
Cui Wenkui hates the accomplice.
He caught the accomplice spy himself.
He caught more than the other groups.
Who would believe that?
Master,
Are you going to bail him out?
No.
Cui Wenkui is known as General Tie.
I couldn't find anything on him.
His independent Brigade
under my nose.
It's his turn to be unlucky.
Master,
Are you interested in his independent Brigade?
Yes.
His independent Brigade
Since he resists the Japanese now,
so he is temporarily cooperating with our 16th Division.
But he doesn’t
regard himself as the 16th Master.
I always wanted to swallow him.
but I couldn't find a chance.
Master.
Cai Zhen
helped you a lot.
Not enough.
If Choi Moon-Kui gets out of prison,
it's my nephew who lit the lantern.
Everything is the same.
We have to prove Cui Wenkui's crime
the independent Brigade is our treasure.
Wonderful.
Good idea, Master.
Independent Brigade
is one third of the team.
How much pay should we get?
When the time comes,
and logistics
will all fall into our pockets.
Come in.
How's your injury?
Nothing serious.
It's just a scratch.
Thank you for sending me to the hospital.
I should thank you.
You saved the people
to save the people from a disaster.
No need to be polite.
I just did what I should.
Please keep your promise.
Of course.
I brought you your favorite food.
Eat.
Do you remember this?
Tell me.
Have you suffered a lot
have you suffered a lot?
No.
I guess you took the buns out.
Stop it.
Get me out of here.
When Bao leaves the city,
I'll let you out right away.
I've been like this since I was a kid.
I fought with him.
You've been siding with him.
Am I your brother?
Of course.
Brother.
Then why do you always side with others?
Ni, you're so pretty.
I think of you every day.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Help!
Stop yelling.
Don't say there's no one here.
Even if there are people,
I won’t be afraid of them.
Because Qinglong Fortress
will be mine soon.
Are you crazy?
How could Qinglong Camp be yours?
This place
will soon be occupied by us Japanese.
Qinglong Camp, Shanzhou City,
and these three levels
will fall into
in our hands.
You are Japanese.
Help! Japanese!
Help! Shut up!
You know what will happen to Er Dan.
If you keep screaming, you'll end up like him.
You killed Erdan!
You bastard!
That's right.
Ni, I really like you.
As long as you follow me,
we will treat you well.
You will have endless glory and wealth.
I don't want any wealth.
Let go of me!
Help! Don't scream!
Help!
No one will save you here.
You belong to me today.
Help!
Move!
Stop!
Who said no one can save her?
Uncle Liu, save me!
He's Japanese.
I've been looking for him for so long.
I didn't expect the biggest spy
is hiding beside me.
That's right.
It's been four years.
you haven't noticed me.
That's because you're too stupid.
Do you know what I represent?
Ghost!
If I didn't keep you alive,
I would have killed you that day.
You can kill me now.
You bastard!
You ghost!
You were the one who attacked me that night.
I didn't kill you that night.
What a pity.
You ruined my plan.
I'll kill you.
You killed so many of our men.
I'm going to kill them today.
and see who dies fast.
I'll kill you today.
Kid, your foot-repair knife
is not enough to tickle me.
Go report to hell.
Good.
Uncle Liu, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Here.
Baoni.
It's okay.
Go home.
Be careful.
What are you doing?
Which unit are you from?
I'm Master 16, Jang Gong-yeon.
From today onwards,
from today on.
Brother.
Is Jang Gong-yeon here?
You'll know soon.
Brigade Commander Cui.
Brigade Commander Cui, we meet again.
But this place is too special.
I knew it was you.
What do you mean?
I heard that Brigadier Cui who guarded Shanzhou
is suspected of collaboration.
As the commander of the frontline of Yu Xi,
I have to investigate it.
Mr. Zhang, you’re a Division Commander.
Can you use your brain?
It's nothing.
You believe it too?
I heard Brigade Commander Cui is called General Tie.
When you're in this cell today,
Are you sure you're fine?
How can you be sure that I'm not okay?
Brigade Commander Cui is in an important position.
It concerns the stability of the army in Shanzhou.
If we don't find out the truth,
I’m afraid the overall situation
will be affected.
Investigate it. How?
What do you mean? Punish me?
Brigade Commander Cui, I advise you
you'd better confess honestly.
your crime of colluding with the rebels.
Mr. Zhang will definitely
for your hard work,
I will put in a good word for you in front of my superior
and punish you lightly.
Jang Gong-yeon.
I know you’re trying to set me up.
You hit me when I was being investigated.
and take away my military power from me, right?
Brigade Commander Cui,
We are both smart people.
Why are you being so harsh?
Your army, my army,
That's the Party's team.
It doesn't matter who leads them.
Jang Gong-yeon.
I saved your life from the swordsman many times.
You're so evil.
Have you lost your conscience?
Brigade Commander Cui, calm down.
Actually, there is another way.
I wonder if Brigade Commander Cui is willing.
If you give your military power
to the 16th Division,
to transfer all weapons, military supplies
and military supplies.
I believe he will do everything he can
to clear your name.
Are you dreaming in broad daylight?
Jang Gong-yeon, let me tell you.
I know you want to expand your team.
I'm not against that.
But you're too evil.
You want to drink blood of soldiers and eat meat.
and oppressed the soldiers' pay.
Do you know how hard our brothers are working on the front line?
How can you let them down?
Choi Moon-Kui!
Don't be so hard on me.
Since we've broken up,
I won't hide it from you.
If you don't confess,
you can’t leave here alive.
Master.
Cui Wenkui is the Brigade Commander appointed by the war zone.
If we go too far,
if we go too far?
It's okay.
As long as he signs and signs,
there's nothing to say about the war zone commander.
Why is he
just like his father?
The stone in the toilet is stinky and hard.
How dare you block my way of making money?
Leave it to me.
Are you done discussing?
Hurry up if you want to fight.
Brigade Commander Cui.
Hurry up.
Brigade Commander Cui, I'm sorry.
Comfortable.
As promised,
our swordsmen have left Shanzhou.
Thank you.
I don't know if I should say this.
Just say it.
Cai has visited you in Shanzhou.
But she was taken away
before I got to the hospital.
But I saved him.
Send someone back for treatment.
Miss Shangguan.
I can see
Jennifer Cai loves you so much.
She misses you all the time.
How could he do something that makes you sad?
Tell him this.
Don't show up in front of me.
Or I'll kill him.
Wen Pei. Wen Pei.
I heard a news on my way back.
Jang Gong-yeon controls the independent Brigade Headquarters.
and interrogated Choi Moon-Kui in prison.
Jang Gong-yeon, that bastard.
I have to go back to save him.
Wait for me.
Master, this kid is really tough.
He broke several sticks.
but they won't let go.
The Cui family is all like this.
If it was so easy,
I wouldn't have been so troublesome back then.
You won't let go?
Fine.
Let's try something else.
Stop!
Who allowed you to abuse your private torture here?
You caught him, Major Chae.
He's charged with treason.
Chief Lu and I are interrogating him.
Any questions?
This is the prisoner of our army.
If you want to ask,
I’ll give you a detailed report
after the investigation.
But if you interfere with our interrogation,
your arms are too long.
We're just helping.
I'm afraid you'll overwork yourself.
No need.
Agent investigation is our duty.
If you are interested in taking this case,
you can say hello to Mr. Dai.
I will hand over the case.
Master.
Mr. Dai
is a living hell who eats people without spitting bones.
He doesn't seem to have a high rank,
But they are all senior officials.
They manage all military affairs.
We can't afford to offend him.
Major Chae.
I'm sorry.
I'm in a hurry.
I don't know what happened.
Please forgive me if I offended you.
Major Chae, please take care of this place.
We'll leave right away.
Let's go.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
They can't do anything to me.
I'm sorry.
I made you suffer.
Let me help you up.
Don't move. Don't move.
Legs.
Go.
Nini.
What happened?
Why are you so depressed?
You're bullying me.
If Uncle Liu hadn't come,
I...
What did you say?
He bullied you again.
I'll get even with him.
Father, you don't have to go.
Uncle Liu killed him.
He's Japanese.
He told me before he died.
that he was Japanese.
how many people know about it now?
Only Uncle Liu and I know.
We haven't had time to tell others.
Father, should we tell my sister first?
to get ready?
Maybe there are Japanese
among the newcomers.
Don't tell anyone about this.
Why?
Nini,
The people in the fortress are dispersed.
Miss Ying has been worried
because of Patriarch.
We shouldn't cause any more trouble.
Leave it to me.
I'll go secretly.
and find these Japanese.
Also,
don't tell your mother about this.
Don't let her worry.
I won't tell her.
I don't want her to worry.
I heard from Jang Gong-yeon
I think he knows our father.
We were young then.
Zhang Gong Yan was the commander of defense in Peking.
used the name of drill
in the name of training.
As the vice mayor of Peking,
once exposed his corruption
to Nanjing Government.
But in the end, because of civil war,
We need the support of these officers.
and just let it go.
How about this?
It’s more convenient for you to be the commander.
Check
what Zhang Gong Yan did in Peking.
Okay.
Take a rest here.
I'll get someone to treat you.
That old man.
He's strong.
Masao Tawahara!
You promised not to hurt them.
Yes, I did promise.
But it was just an accident.
I didn't expect
that stupid ghost would be so foolish.
How dare he hit on your daughter?
Now that he's dead,
He deserves it.
But his identity
has alerted the people in the fortress.
If I act out of line again,
I will be suspected.
I can't go on like this.
If you want to take any action,
you can send another person.
I’ll find a way
to give him the position of Patriarch.
Are you telling the truth?
I think you're out of your mind.
If an outsider
become
the leader of Qinglong Fortress so easily.
Then why should I
to make conditions for you
I asked you to sit here.
You're more foolish than him.
Because you're here,
because you're here.
If you lose this umbrella,
do you think you can be so casual?
But now...
Mr. He.
To be honest,
you've been doing well.
You're the best candidate for this position.
Hang in there for a few more days.
you can get rid of these burdens soon.
By then,
will you sit here?
or if you want anything,
just tell me.
I will promise you.
I want nothing.
I just want my wife and daughter's safety.
This is my bottom line.
They know nothing about this.
I will never let them get hurt
because of my mistake.
Mr. He,
I care about them more than you do.
After all,
you'll cooperate with us.
So,
I won't let anything happen to them.
Don't worry.
Our men will protect her in secret.
However,
there's one more thing
for me.
Anything else?
We had planned
the National Party and the swordsman
and the swordsman.
but someone ruined it.
I want you to kill her now.
You mean Shangguan Eagle?
Yes, that's her.
Just like her father,
as her father.
With her around,
she'll be a disaster to the Imperial Army sooner or later.
You can't kill her.
Mr. He, let me remind you.
She is not your family.
Besides, if she knows
you helped us Japanese kill her father,
You should know
what will happen to you.
I owe Leader.
It doesn’t matter
who killed me.
If I can die in Shangguan Eagle's hands,
I'm willing to die.
Fine.
You can die.
If you die,
I'll take care of your wife and daughter.
If you can let Shangguan eagle go,
I can make a deal with you
to make a deal with you.
The biggest secret.
Okay, tell me.
I have two maps.
related to the secret of the treasures of Qinglong Hideout.
Shangguan Bao can lead 100,000 swordsmen
because of this huge fortune,
with this huge fortune.
Promise me first.
Sure.
If this secret you mentioned is very valuable,
I can promise you to let her go.
But let me tell you.
If Shangguan Eagle gets in our way again,
then
no gift can save her life.
Masao Tahara.
You must keep your promise this time.
Don't worry.
I’m a man of my word.
Qinglong Fortress really has a treasure.
I was wondering
last so long.
I see.
I didn't expect that I've been in Shaanxi for so long.
I know nothing about the treasure.
Come here.
Take your time.
I missed.
Let me teach you.
Move your body to the side.
Relax your legs. Wide your shoulders.
Look at the target.
Your body and your hand should be in a corner.
Eyes, accuracy, and goal.
It has to be a line.
Hold it tight.
Shoot!
I still missed.
Let's stop practicing.
I'm not good enough.
I just hit him a few times.
He said he's not good enough.
The world is in chaos now.
You must learn to save yourself.
Let me teach you.
Side.
Hold your hands tight.
Okay.
Shoot.
Again.
Go on.
I think there's no bullet.
It's okay. We need bullets.
Keep practicing.
You can't rush to learn shooting.
To practice shooting.
Stop! What are you doing?
Ask Liu for bullets.
Liu is not here.
He won't be in charge of the arsenal anymore.
When did that happen?
Why didn’t I know?
Mr. He gave the order.
Ask him if you don’t understand.
My father...
Stop! Stop!
No one can enter
no one is allowed to enter.
Can't I, Shangguan Eagle?
I'm new here.
I don't know him.
Go back.
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
Uncle.
Why do you forbid everyone from entering the firearm warehouse?
Eagle.
After the last incident,
I wanted to strictly control the gun
To extract guns,
must be approved by our boss.
and clear registration.
so that no one would hold a gun
and do evil things.
But you gave the right to manage the warehouse
to outsiders.
Since my father became the head,
Liu has been managing the arsenal.
Is it inappropriate
to do this?
Eagle, we are brothers after entering the fortress.
There's no difference inside and outside.
Liu did contribute to the fortress.
But he has been working hard for so many years.
It’s time to take a rest.
so that the others in the Fortress
to get familiar with the business.
This is also a way to save talents.
Do you think Mr. He is right?
You're right.
Eagle.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
A few days ago,
you stopped
stopped the conflict between swordsmen and the army.
and helped the people
for the people of Shaanxi.
But I accidentally offended
Japanese agents who want to make trouble in secret.
I'm afraid they might harm you.
So I want you to hide down the mountain for a while.
If they don't come to me,
I want to find them too.
Those Japanese are secretly destroying Qinglong Hideout.
and made our village
in a mess.
We should have settled this long ago.
Eagle,
You're the only child of your father.
If something happens to you,
how can Mr. He
face your father after he died?
My father once said
one will die.
or less than a feather or more important than Mount Tai.
If I really died because of anti-Japanese,
I would have died a worthy death.
My father won't blame you.
In fact, asking you to go down the mountain
Uncle He has his own motive.
Look.
The fortress is getting more and more unsafe.
Ni
was threatened by the Japanese again and again.
Although Liu is a righteous man,
Kill that brat.
Who knows if there's another one?
So,
I want Eagle
to escort Meixiang’s aunt and Ni
to hide in the pool.
Got it.
Leave this to me.
After sending them there,
I will come back.
to fight the Japanese with you.
Thank you, Young Lady Zhen Zhu.
Uncle, what are you doing?
We're family.
Major, did you find anything?
Nothing.
Is that old man fooling us again?
Ikezawa. Yes.
Send a telegram to the special class.
Ask the superior to send experts to help crack it.
Yes.
The pool.
Why?
It's so far away.
for so long.
Is something going to happen in the village?
Don’t think too much.
What can happen in the village?
Are you coming with us?
Where can I go?
Master.
We've been married for 20 years.
We know each other well.
Ni and I
leave you.
Why did you send us
to such a faraway place?
And it's been so long.
Tell me honestly.
Is there a big threat?
I asked you to make this decision.
I'll go with you.
With her by your side,
we can take care of each other on the way.
Master,
Although I'm not a smart woman,
but I feel like a mirror.
Is the Japanese coming?
You asked me to escape with Nini first.
Right?
Stop talking.
Just listen to me.
Go pack up.
Gosh.
Actors.
and actors.
Su Tianhui, Yang Wanlin, Zhao Dongliang, Chen Yile, Wang Lusheng.
Yue, Wang, Yang Ziyi, Tian Chenzhe, Deng Kai. Mei Liang Dong.
Li, Yu Hongda, Tian Guofeng, Gong, Fan. Cheng Kaiyan.
Sun Zhaoqi, Li Shengseng, Yang Haoyu, Callow.
Yang Ziyi, Tian Chenzhe, Deng Kai, Mei Liangdong
to perform.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao, Sun Haochun.
Zhang Hongbo, Gong Jianfeng, Li Kaiwu, Zhuang, Tao Sun Hao.
Wang Jinjun Liu Jiawen.
Ji, Chao, Zhao Zhigang, Kung, Ji Youyi. Peng Zhenfu.
Xu Fu and Wu Jianyu Zhang Guangyan Sun Yuanwen Chang Qing.
Wu Jinxing, Feng Yonghao, Wei Long, Deng Bao Quan.
Qin Haosen, Liu Mingjun, Zhang Lianglin.
Li Jinyang, Zhang Jianing.
Li Zhendong, Chi, Rui, Zhang Ke'er, Yang Junjie. Cui Yuseok.
Zhao Jianhao, Li Xiaoyan, Dong Yuanqi
Staff table.
Director team.
The production team.
Feng Xiaogang.
Photography team.
Lighting Team.
The clothing team.
Shi Jangyeong.
Li Zhenzheng.
The dressing team.
Art team.
Props team.
Ye Youth.
Set team.
Yang Longfei.
Action team.
Fireworks.
The gun team.
The recording team.
Wang Wenbo.
The venue team.
Driver team.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Kang Jiping.
Li Zhenmin, Dou Xingbin, Wei Ran Jia, Zong Changshun Rong Xi.
Wei Zidian, Qiao Chunsheng, Yang, Tao, Chen Jianfen Jiang Jiping.
Wang Bao Cheung, Su Gao Feng, Liu Deyu, Zhai Yongming. Zou Youwei.
Zhang Chenggui, Su Mingxin, Liu Hongxing, Di Yuping Xu Guanglle.
Xu Ian, Zhang Shou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Teng Tie Yan, Xu Ian, Zhang Shou Qiang, Yang Yijiang
Ge Wenlong, Song Yongqiang, Wang Daxiong, Yang Ziguang Zhang Jian Ping.
Cut.
[Lee Moon-jung]
Late production.
ZMCG.
Beijing Zhuma Chenguang Culture Co., Ltd.
dubber
Music production.
Theme song, Hero.
Rex.
Singer: Wei Ningfeng Qin Yidan
Thank you, Mr. Wang Xiao, for the title of this drama.
Thank you.
Shandong Blumund Red Film Club. [National 4A Scene Area]
Henan Juntong Car Co., Ltd.
Jintang Jun Kin.
Shanzhou District Public Government
Shanzhou District Civil Government
The People's government of Xizhang Village, Shanzhou District.
The Civil Affairs of Xizhang Village, Seozhou District.
The temple in Shanzhou District.
[Seobu Village Committee of Lingbao City]
Original store is in a fork.
Zhou Jiajun's kiln in the city.
The village committee of Zhen Kui Village.
The legal consultant service unit.
Henan Lu Da Law Firm.
Special cooperation unit.
There are three Municipal Committee in total.
The People's Government
There are three branches in total.
There are three marketing departments in total.
The Commission of Shanzhou
The People's Government of Shanzhou District
Zhongtong Municipal County Commission.
Henan Henan Yunyang Liquor Co., Ltd.
The People's Government of Laji County.
Henan Henan Boutique Co., Ltd.
The Cultural Responsibility Co., Ltd.
[Sanmen Lanhu City Wetland Park]
Sanmen Cultural Tourism Investment Group.
Yang Tingxuan.
The guidance unit.
Learning to strengthen our country.
The circulation unit.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Control unit.
Henan Sandao Movie Development Co., Ltd.
[Joint Film Co., Ltd.]
[Joint filming unit]
The PR Department of Gansu Provincial Committee
Henan Provincial Radio Station.
[Henan Provincial Literature and Arts Association]
TV station.
Henan Provincial Film Association.
Henan Film and TV Group Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Xiamen) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Beijing Times, Yishi Cultural Technology Co., Ltd.
Gansu Lanyi Culture Co., Ltd.
Hebei Army Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
Production unit.
Henan Elephant Film Production Co., Ltd.
Henan Movie Development Co., Ltd.
Qijin (Quan Zhou) Cultural Media Co., Ltd.
First reward Zhang Bing.
Reward Zhang Bing first.